If you have a 10 number password,
then with software with the cryptographic calculation
to brute force attack your environment,
it will take five seconds to crack.
Most people think eight characters with
multiple different characters is pretty secure
and that's kind of standard for password requirements.
But if someone really wants it, it may take them 35 days,
we'd rather be more secure than that.
If you have 16 characters with one upper case and one special character.
For example,
this is more secure because you have
upper and lower case characters and special characters
to crack this, it will take about 152,000 years.
So just by following a good password policy and appropriate procedures,
we can improve our password security immensely.